Guide to the Fay Chiang Papers TAM.748
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Poets and Writers - Nathan Cummings Foundation, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Poets and Writers - Readings/Workshops, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 1-2, Flat-file-folder 1)
- Poets and Writers - Writers Exchange Program (WEX), 1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 3-4, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 6)
- Poets and Writers - Writers Exchange Program (WEX) -- Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1998-2000 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Poetry Festivals, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 5, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 7)
- Press About Fay Chiang, 1996-1997, 2010-2011 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Project Reach, 1997-1998, 2001-2003, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
- Project Reach - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 2011, 2016 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Project Reach - Correspondence -- Adolph and Esther Gottlieb Emergency Grant [RESTRICTED], 2016 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Project Reach - Fay Chiang's Birthday Party, circa 2010s; cuid42577 (Box 17, Folder 1, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_11)
- Project Reach - Fertile Grounds/Survival Project, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Project Reach - Peer Counseling/Facilitation and Arts Workshop, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Projects, 2016 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Protest Photographs, circa 2010-2014 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- A Railroad on Gold Mountain, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Revolution in the 21st Century (Boggs Center), 2012 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Robert Liyanto, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Scrapbooks, undated (Box 42, Box Shared Tamiment 169, Folder 5)
- Seoul International Writer's Festival, 2012 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Serve the People: Making Asian America in the Long Sixties (Karen L. Ishizuka) - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 2015 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Serve the People: Making Asian America in the Long Sixties (Karen L. Ishizuka) - Draft, 2015 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Setting leaves afire (Taiyo), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Seven Continents/Nine Lives (Monologue), 2007 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Seventeen Syllables and Other Stories (Hisaye Yamamoto), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Sketchbook, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
- "The Special Situtation, problems, advantages, wonders, difficulties, etc… of being an Asian woman artist" (article by Fay Chiang), 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Synin/Heart: A Monologue by Fay Chiang, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Terence Sheehan Mix CD, circa 2004-2006; cuid42578 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_1)
- Trans Art Tokyo, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Two Boots and a Ball Gown, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
- Video Projects, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- The Whole Heart Mixtape Taiyo, 2005; cuid42579 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_748_ER_6)
- Zero Capital, 2008-2009 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Zero Capital - Border Statements, China-Burma (Myanmar) Border Project, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Zero Capital - CLUSTERBOMB! Exhibition, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Zero Capital - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 2008-2011 (Box 38, Folder 11)